Interactions have three different types
Critical
Serious
Moderate
Critical
Do not take this combination together
Contact your doctor, pharmacist or care team
to discuss this combination
Severe or life-threatening side effects may occur
In rare cases, they may be taken together
with specific approval from your care team
Serious
Discuss this combination with your care team
Taking them together may cause significent side effects
or cause medications to not work as well
your care team may recommend
changes to your treatment plan
Ask your care team what to watch
for when taking this combination
Moderate
In certain cases
this combination may be taken together
When taken together
side effects may occur
medications may not work as well
Your care team may recommend
changes to your treament plan
Ask your care team what to watch for when taking this combination